jackcow.com 2013-06-05

# Jackcow.com

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the JackCow website, www.JackCow.com (referred to hereafter as the "Website").

The Website is provided by Forum Digital Sdn Bhd, a Malaysian incorporated private limited liability company (referred to hereafter as "us" or "we").

We are committed to protecting your privacy online.

Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (referred to hereafter as the "User") and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at support@jackcow.com.

 ***PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THISPRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.***

### 1\. Changes to Privacy Policy

1.1 We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the Privacy Policy section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website.

1.2 It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

### 2\. Type of Information Collected and Use of Collected Information

2.1 We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally IdentifiableI nformation and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

2.2 Personally Identifiable Information

2.2.1 Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific End User.When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating anaccount, ordering and/or purchasing a product or service from us or ourpartners, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums,entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, filling outa survey, posting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, requestinginformation about our services, submitting an affiliate agreement, applying fora job, posting a video or signing up for special offers from third partiesthrough the Website (collectively, referred to as �Identification Activities�),we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optionalfor you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in anIdentification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certainpersonal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, ICnumber, mailing address (including zip code), email address, telephone number, dateof birth, occupation and income level.

2.2.2 When you orderand purchase products or services including vouchers, we may also ask you toprovide us with your credit card number, expiration date and authenticationcodes or related information. Depending on the activity, some of theinformation we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some isidentified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for aparticular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage inthat activity.

2.2.3 We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you,administer sweepstakes and contests, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our products and services offerings, and to tailor your experience with third parties as provided in Item 3 of this Privacy Policy. For example, if you send our customer service an email we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website.

2.2.4 If you use our Website to send information of a product or service or an offer to another person,we may store your personal information, and the personal information of anyrecipient. We may use that other person�s contact information to allow him orher to view and accept your gift or to allow the recipient to access theinformation you requested we send.

2.2.5 We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

2.3 Non-Personally Identifiable Information

2.3.1 Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific End User.This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (referred to hereafter as �URL�) of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol (referred to hereafter as �IP�)address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixeltags.

2.3.2 We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

2.3.3 We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising,content, and programming.

### 3\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Informationwith other parties except as provided below:

3.1 We may shareyour information with Affiliated Vendors. We provide some products or servicesjointly with particular vendors. These are known as �Affiliated Vendors�. We share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliated Vendors in order to help them provide you with better service and track the value of our program. Sharing this Information will allow an Affiliated Vendor to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a Vendor if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the Vendor involved in that Identification Activity. For example, if you purchase a promotional voucher for a particular restaurant, we may share your name, email address and city with that restaurant.

3.2 We may share your information with JackCow Merchants. From time to time, we provide offersfrom particular merchants (referred to as �JackCow Merchants�) who, as part of the offer, request information on JackCow customers who purchased the offer. Inthose cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with JackCowMerchant. Sharing this information will allow a JackCow Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a JackCow Merchant if you engage in anIdentification Activity, and then only to the JackCow Merchant involved in that Identification Activity.

3.4 We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such JackCowMerchants. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicatewith you for the purposes of the specific promotion with JackCow, we do nothave any responsibility for the actions of the JackCow Merchants, and theactions of the JackCow Merchants are not in our control.

3.5 We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers. We provide someof our services and products through third parties. These Third Party Service Providers perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service.

3.6 We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies (referred to hereafter as �Affiliates�) with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a service, we release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for theservice and, if applicable, release your address to the delivery service todeliver the service. Likewise, we may release an Affiliate�s information to ourbank to send out a payment. We encourage Affiliated Vendors, Affiliated Businesses, Marketing Partners and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.

3.7 We may share your information in a Change of Ownership. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company or person. If this occurs, the successor company or person would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, such Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy (as revised).

3.8 We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order, enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

### 4\. Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

4.1 We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Third PartyService Providers Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with Third Party Advertisers or Third Party Advertising Companies and other parties as provided below:

4.2 We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to our and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

4.3 We may also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

### 5\. Updating and Correcting Information

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by accessing your account and editing your user profile. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have your user profile deleted by sending an email to support@jackcow.com.

### 6\. User Choices on Collection and Use of Information

6.1 As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website.

6.2 As a condition of purchase of our products and services, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and services and promotional offers.

6.3 You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. Administrative Emails relate to a User�sactivity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User�saccount, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services.

6.4 In contrastto Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect toPromotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise our products and services,including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services ofour Advertisers, JackCow Merchants and Affiliates.

6.5 If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out ofreceiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at support@jackcow.com, by writing to us atthe address contained herein, or by hitting the �unsubscribe� button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address,email address, and what Promotional Emails you do not want to receive.

### 7\. Security of Information

7.1 We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security ofPersonally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone and that you change your password periodically.

7.2 We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it istransmitted to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

### 8\. Data Tracking

8.1 Cookies. To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we may store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User�s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on.

8.2 We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. Wehave no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Third Party Advertiser.

8.3 Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly.

8.4 Other Tracking Devices.

8.4.1 We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions.

8.4.2 We may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf.

8.4.3 Pixel tags andweb beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, orin our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specificaction. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags andweb beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action.

8.4.4 Pixel tagsallow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions andperformance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by ourAffiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes.

### 9\. JackCow Promotions

9.1 When you enter a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest hosted by us or sponsored by usand/or our many partners, we ask for your name, address, and email address. You may be asked to provide additional information or to answer certain questions, some of which may be optional.

9.2 We may contact you in connection with a particular promotion, such as a sweepstakes orcontest, in order to update you of your status, administer the promotion, let you know that a promotion has ended, and for other purposes.

9.3 Promotions that are hosted on the Website may be sponsored by us, may be co-sponsored by us and another company, or may be sponsored by companies other than us. Some or all of the data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor(s)or companies indicated on the entry form. Promotions that are hosted by a third party may collect and use information alone or in conjunction with us.

9.4 The nature of this information sharing policy will be indicated on the entry form. If information is collected and used by a third party, you will need to see their privacy policy to understand how that information may be used.

9.5 If data will be shared, then there will be notice prior to the time of data collection or transfer.

9.6 Some promotions, sweepstakes or contests may use cookies in order to track your progress and number of entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. When you participate in a promotion sponsored or hosted by us, you are subject the official rules of that promotion.

### 10\. Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites

10.1 This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices.

10.2 If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the websites privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

### 11\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues : Children

11.1 Minors under the age of 18 may not use the Website.

11.2 We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 18.

11.3 No part of theWebsite is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

### 12\. Public Areas

12.1 We may provide areas on our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others, or can review products, vendors, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others.

12.2 If you post your email address along with a public vendor review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information.
